{
    "subject": "resource/Southern_Nigeria_Protectorate",
    "predicate": "ontology/currency",
    "object": "resource/Pound_sterling",
    "human_readable": "The currency of Southern Nigeria Protectorate is Pound sterling.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9352592825889587,
            "question": "What factors might have influenced the choice of Pound sterling as currency for the Southern Nigeria Protectorate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9169414043426514,
            "question": "What is the historical significance of using Pound sterling in the Southern Nigeria Protectorate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8926394581794739,
            "question": "What was the currency of the Southern Nigeria Protectorate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8517985939979553,
            "question": "Which country's currency was used in the Southern Nigeria Protectorate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.80948805809021,
            "question": "How did the use of Pound sterling affect trade and economic relations within the Southern Nigeria Protectorate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6855643391609192,
            "question": "What type of monetary system did the Southern Nigeria Protectorate use?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5521488189697266,
            "question": "Besides Nigeria, were there other territories that used Pound sterling?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5074068903923035,
            "question": "When was the Southern Nigeria Protectorate established?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4256891906261444,
            "question": "What is the current currency used in Nigeria?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3070506453514099,
            "question": "What are some examples of countries that have historically used Pound sterling?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The currency of Southern Nigeria Protectorate is Pound sterling.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9207_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the current currency used in Nigeria?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9207_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was the Southern Nigeria Protectorate established?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9207_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Besides Nigeria, were there other territories that used Pound sterling?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9207_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9207_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9207_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9207_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9207_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9207_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9207_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9207_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9207_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9207_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9207_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents contain information about the Colony and Protectorate of Southern Nigeria, which mentions that \"The British pound sterling was the official currency of the new colony.\" (from file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_9207/re-ranker-msmarco/6.txt)"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\n**Explanation:** The documents mention that the British pound sterling was used as the official currency of the Colony and Protectorate of Southern Nigeria. Therefore, it supports the statement that the currency of Southern Nigeria Protectorate is Pound Sterling."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}